<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eventify</string>
    <string name="upcomming_nmusic_events">Upcomming \nMusic Events</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="select_an_event_category_to_view_the_events_happening_soon_related_to_the_category_n_click_on_the_event_you_would_like_to_book_a_ticket_for_n_view_the_event_details_and_click_on_book_ticket_to_generate_your_ticket_only_1_ticket_can_be_booked_per_account_n_upon_generating_the_final_ticket_you_may_click_the_back_to_home_button_n_click_on_the_icon_to_view_the_side_menu_bar_to_view_your_booked_tickets_click_on_the_my_bookings_button_and_you_may_view_all_your_booked_tickets_there_n_click_on_log_out_to_log_out_of_your_account_n_you_may_log_back_in_using_the_same_e_mail_to_get_your_booked_tickets_back_n">- Select an event category to view the events happening soon related to the category.\n - Click on the event you would like to book a ticket for.\n - View the Event Details and click on Book Ticket to generate your ticket. Only 1 ticket can be booked per account.\n - Upon generating the final ticket you may click the Back To Home Button.\n - Click on the “☰” icon to view the side menu bar. To view your booked tickets, click on the “My Bookings” button and you may view all your booked tickets there.\n - Click on “Log Out” to log out of your account.\n - You may log back in using the same e-mail to get your booked tickets back.\n</string>
    <string name="click_on_the_event_you_would_like_add_this_will_add_the_event_on_the_user_accounts_and_will_make_the_event_available_for_booking_when_a_user_logs_in_n_you_may_add_as_many_of_the_available_events_as_you_d_like_n_click_on_the_icon_to_view_the_side_menu_bar_you_may_reset_the_event_additions_you_ve_made_by_clicking_on_the_reset_additions_button_n_you_may_log_out_of_your_account_by_clicking_on_the_log_out_button_it_is_not_necessary_to_reset_or_to_not_reset_your_additions_before_logging_out_n_your_progress_will_be_saved_for_when_you_log_back_in_n">- Click on the event you would like add. This will add the event on the user accounts and will make the event available for booking when a user logs in.\n - You may add as many of the available events as you’d like.\n - Click on the “☰” icon to view the side menu bar. You may reset the event additions you’ve made by clicking on the “Reset Additions” button.\n - You may Log Out of your account by clicking on the “Log Out” button. It is not necessary to reset or to not reset your additions before logging out.\n - Your progress will be saved for when you log back in.\n</string>

</resources>